ontrapages.com 2019-03-28

# Ontraport Legal | Terms & Conditions

Responsibilities and Management  
Ontraport has designated our legal department to oversee compliance with the EU and Swiss Privacy Shield program and the GDPR. This team shall review and approve any material changes to this program as necessary. Any questions, concerns, or comments regarding this Policy also may be directed to  _[gdpr@ontraport.com](mailto:gdpr@ONTRAPORT.com "Link: mailto:gdpr@ONTRAPORT.com")_. 

Ontraport will maintain, monitor, test, and upgrade information security policies, practices, and systems to assist in protecting the personal data that it collects. Ontraport personnel will receive training, as applicable, to effectively implement this Policy. 

Collection and Use of Personal Data  
Ontraport provides various products services to its customers, some of whom are EU citizens. Ontraport collects personal data from individuals when they purchase our products, fill out a form on our website, log in to their account, complete surveys, request information or otherwise communicate with us. For example, Ontraport customers may choose to seek live support or post to a message board.

The personal data that we collect may vary based on the customer’s interaction with our website and request for our services. Generally, Ontraport collects contact information, including names, email and physical addresses, phone numbers, company names and more. We also collect payment information including credit card information. Customers have the option to log into their accounts online and to request service online, including through a live support option; we will collect information that they choose to provide to us through these portals.

When Ontraport customers or non-customers use our services or website online, we will collect their IP address and browser type, along with contact information and any other information that the person chooses to submit through our website.

The information that we collect from customers is used for selling the products and services they buy from us, managing transactions, reporting, invoicing, renewals, other operations related to providing services and products to our customers.

Ontraport also serves its customers as a service provider. In our capacity as a service provider, we will receive, store, and/or process personal data. In such cases, we are acting as a data processor and will process the personal information on behalf of and under the direction of our partners and/or agents. The information that we collect from our customers in this capacity is used for managing transactions, reporting, invoicing, renewals, other operations related to providing services to our customers.

Ontraport uses the personal data that we collect from our customers for the following business purposes, without limitation:
